[{"answer": "And this is exactly the kind of behavior that will give them an excuse to do it", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Don't apologize, my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You ever get any false positives? Someone intends to kill his boss or his wife, but they never go through with it.  How do the precogs tell the difference", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Then why can't they see rapes, or assaults... or suicides", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "To them", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Really?  You've never been inside", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "So give him a tour.  He doesn't know enough to ask the right questions", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "He's not.  He's looking for a flaw in us, my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The victim's name is my friend", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I've got no address", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You're not gonna kill me", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I'm not getting halo'd", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Everybody runs", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Everybody runs", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You don't have to chase me, my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You said they're destroyed", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What safe place is that", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I said the record is destroyed. The original report exists for all time.  I designed the system so that whenever a report occurred, it would be stored in a safe place", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "The safest place of all", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "So you haven't seen his apartment", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Have you been there recently", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You mean after he lost your son", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "But my friend was with him at the pool", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You said in your divorce papers that he tried to kill himself", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What was it then", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I'm impressed, my friend.  You're on the lam, but you still got the time and energy to slice off a little jerky for yourself", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " She's a precog", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "They could have been put away. my friend could have found them", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I was a Treasury Agent for eight years.  Why", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "He's dead, my friend", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Nothing.  I didn't kill him", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Oh, God, what did you do", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Then how did he", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I always wondered what the world would be like.  But now that I've seen it, I don't need to see any more.  It's all right.  Once I'm in the tank, I won't remember any of this", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I am going back.  I see myself there", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Then who was he", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Found?  Where", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "my friend said something about him being set up because he", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "He also said my friend was a fake", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "It's a single stream, from the female only, with no time or incident data", "docId": "MINORITY_REPORT_--_May_16th_2001_revised_draft_by_Scott_Frank.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Meaning whatever this is, it ain't the future.  It already happened", "qsentId": 42}]